(Howard:)Sheldon, you're wrong.
(Howard:)Wolverine was not born
with bone claws.
(Sheldon:)Howard, you know me to be
a very smart man.
(Sheldon:)Don't you think if I were wrong,
I'd know it?
(Howard:)-First of all--
-Give it up.
(Raj:)You're arguing with a crazy person.
(Sheldon:)I'm not crazy.
My mother had me tested.
(Leonard:)-Hey, guys.
-What are you doing here?
What? It's new-comic-book night.
Since you and Penny hooked up...
(Raj:)...we thought you two would be having
bouncy naked yum-yum night.
(Leonard:)There's more to life than sex, Raj.
(Howard:)Who had Leonard flames out
in 24 hours?
(Sheldon:)I did.
(Leonard:)Nothing flamed out.
(Leonard:)We don't have to have sex
every night.
(Howard:)You don't have to,
but it's highly recommended.
(Raj:)Take advantage
of that window of opportunity...
(Raj:)...before it slams shut
on your little dinky.
(Leonard:)It's not a matter of opportunity.
(Leonard:)We're getting to know each other.
There's a learning curve.
What's to learn?
You get naked, do nasty things.
(Howard:)Then somebody makes scrambled eggs
and salami. Easy-peasy.